Finding Aid for the Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature (TISL)
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature (TISL)
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0441
14.28 linear_feet
Scope and Content
The Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature (TISL) Records consist of 13.34 linear feet of materials collected by TISL alumni from its earliest inception in 1966 through the present. The collection is divided into three series; Series I. TISL Publications & Related Organizations; Series II. General Assemblies; and Series III. Oversize Materials.
Series I. TISL Publications & Related Organizations is comprised of newsletters published by TISL, the organizations constitution, and material from other states student legislatures.
Series II. General Assemblies is the largest consisting of reports, bills, correspondence, and manuals gathered during each of the assemblies. This series provides the best documentation of the organization and continues to grow with additions by former TISL members.
Series III. Oversize Materials is made up of a few large items such as a copy of the Tennessee State Seal, House bills, and a Senate bill.
Biographical/Historical Note
The Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature is a statewide organization that seeks to engage college students in government and public affairs through participation in a political process that replicates existing state institutions.
TISL conducts a General Assembly annually in the legislative chambers of the State Capitol, including the election of officers to govern and preside for the coming year. A Senate and House of Representatives composed of college students from across the state considers legislation drafted and sponsored by students. The participants may be engaged for a year doing research and drafting of proposed legislation and resolutions.
Many TISL bills have eventually become state law, and many TISL alumni are in public service, including legislators, judges and Tennessee constitutional officers.
TISL's judicial branch is the Tennessee Intercollegiate Supreme Court. The TISL Foundation also sponsors the Appellate Moot Court Collegiate Challenge (AMC3), a moot appellate court competition for undergraduates.
The organizational meeting of TISL was held on the Vanderbilt campus in 1966, and the 1st General Assembly was at the State Capitol later the same year. Charles Bone Sr., a Vanderbilt undergraduate, was a founder and was Governor of the 2nd General Assembly in 1967. Also instrumental in the founding were Dr. Douglas Carlisle of The University of Tennessee at Knoxville and Phillip Moffitt of UTK, who was the first Governor.
The Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature was incorporated in the State of Tennessee in 1968, mostly through the efforts of Vanderbilt undergraduate M. Baker Wyche, who served as TISL Secretary of State. He also published the first Journal of the Proceedings in 1968. That has become the annual TISL Blue Book.
The 1968 charter was superseded in 1976 by a charter for the Tennessee Intercollegiate State Legislature Foundation, which continues in operation. The TISL Foundation was granted 501(c)(3) status by the Internal Revenue Service in 1977 as an educational organization.
Vanderbilt Library Special Collections became the repository for TISL archives in 1979.
TISL was entirely student run until after 2002, when increased management challenges and a break in continuity caused the student General Assembly to create an independent Board of Directors to govern the organization. That board is composed of a majority of TISL alumni plus two student-elected officers.
- Series 1: TISL Publications & Related Organizations
  - Early Constitutions (Box 1)
    - Original TISL Constitution, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Early TISL Constitutions (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - TISL Constitution, 1973 I (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - TISL Constitution, 1973 II (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - TISL Constitution, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - TISL Printed Constitution, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - TISL Newsletter (Box 2)
    - TISL Newsletter Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 1, No. 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 1, No. 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 1, No. 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 1, No. 4 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - TISL Statesman Copy Vol. 2, No. 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - TISL Statesman Copy Vol. 2, No. 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - TISL Statesman Copy Vol. 2, No. 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - TISL Statesman Copy Vol. 2, No. 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - TISL Statesman Copy Vol. 2, No. 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - TISL Statesman Copy Vol. 2, No. 6 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 2, No. 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 2, No. 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 2, No.3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - TISL Newsletter (Box 3)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 2, No. 4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 2, No. 5 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 2, No. 6 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 3, No. 1 (September, 1978) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 3, No. 1 (Winter Issue) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 3, No. 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 4, No. 2 (February, 1980) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - TISL Statesman Vol. 4, No. 2 (August, 1980) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - TISL Update Vol. 1, No. 2 (9-3-1980) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - TISL Update Vol. 1, No. 3 (10-21-1980) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - TISL Update 20th G.A. (1983) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Related Collegiate Organizations (Box 4)
    - YMCA Tennessee Youth Legislature (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina Student Legislature- General (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina Student Legislature, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina Student Legislature, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Student Legislature-1976 (Duplicates) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Florida Student Legislature (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Georgia Student Legislature (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Louisiana Student Legislature (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Oklahoma Student Legislature (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - South Carolina Student Legislature (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Other Mock Legislatures (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Tennessee Student Association (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Southern Universities Student Government Association (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Series II: TISL General Assemblies
  - Early TISL General Assemblies-1st-4th (Box 5)
    - Moffitt Interview (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 2nd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Journal of Proceedings 2nd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Press Release 2nd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous 2nd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence-M. Baker Wyche III 3rd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Notebook M. Baker Wyche III 3rd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Financial 3nd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings 3rd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Charter of Incorporation (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 3rd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Delegate & Officer Lists 3rd G.A. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - DeJarnatt Administration 4th G.A. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Early TISL General Assemblies-5th-8th (Box 6)
    - 5th G.A. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 6th G.A. General (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 6th G.A. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bills 6th G.A. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 7th G.A Fleming Administration. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bills 7th G.A. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Harris Administration 8th G.A. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - TN State Legislature Manuals (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 10th General Assembly (AKA 9th G.A.) (Box 7)
    - 10th G.A. General (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Member Schools (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Lists (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - News (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Full-Time Enrollment Figures TN Colleges (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - House Representation (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Cabinet Minutes (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - TN Maps (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - MSU Delegation (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Priority Legislation (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Bills (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Duplicate Bills (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 12th General Assembly (Box 8)
    - General-12th G.A. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Welcome From Speaker of House (Lillard) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bonita Wilson Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Randy Eaves Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Mike Rorie Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - David Lillard Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Financial (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Forms (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Roster of Officers (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Executive Council (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Delegate Information Sheets (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Committees (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Carslile Award (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Board of Advisors (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Full-Time Enrollment Figures (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Budget (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - News Notes (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Photo-Sanford & Herron (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Stationery (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - House Joint Resolution 247—Commending TISL (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Senate Bill 12—Commending TISL (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - 12th G.A. Bill Drafts (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 12th General Assembly (Box 9)
    - Bills 001-067 (Excluding 047) (Box 9)
  - 13th General Assembly (Box 10)
    - General 13th General Assembly (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Convention Details (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 13th G.A. Handouts (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Letter of Welcome (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Officers (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Staff Members (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - TISL Bill Format (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - G.A. Information Handouts (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Dodd-Herron Award (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Carson-Newman (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Cleveland State (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - East TN State University (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - King College (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Knoxville College (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Lincoln Memorial (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Maryville College (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Milligan College (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Roane State (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Scarritt College (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Sewanee (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Tusculum College (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - UT Knoxville (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Walters State (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Student Government Directory (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 13th G.A. (Box 11)
    - Incoming Correspondence, Lillard I (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Incoming Correspondence, Lillard II (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Lillard I (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Lillard II (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Greg Gallagher (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Marc Norman (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Bonita Wilson (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Other (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - House and Senate Certificates (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Appointment Certificates (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - TISL Charter (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 89th Tennessee General Assembly Resolution Congratulating TISL (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Postal Permit (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - TISL Foundation 13th GA (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - TISL Memos (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 13th G.A. (Box 12)
    - TISL Executive Board (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Executive Council 13th G.A. I (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Executive Council 13th G.A. II (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - State Board of Regents Visitation Task Force (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Bert Bowes (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - TISL/SGA Officers (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - TISL Roster of Officers (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - TISL Advisory Board (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Delegate Directory (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Delegate Info Sheets (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - News Notes Spring 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - TISL Publications (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - TISL Parliamentary Workshops (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 13th G.A. (Box 13)
    - TISL Seal (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Forms (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Committees (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Stationery (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lillard Special File I (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Lillard Special File II (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 13th G.A. Bills I (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 13th G.A. Bills II (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Slides 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Photographs & Negatives (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Blue Books (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 13th G.A. Alumni (Box 14)
    - Alumni General Info (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Lists (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Data Forms (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Alumni-Aquinas Junior College (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Alumni-Austin Peay State University (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Alumni-Belmont (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Alumni-Carson-Newman College (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Alumni-Christian Brothers College (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Alumni-Cleveland State Community College (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Alumni-David Lipscomb (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Alumni-East TN State University (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Alumni-Lane College (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Alumni-Lee College (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Alumni-Memphis State University (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Alumni-Middle Tennessee State University (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Alumni-Milligan College (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Alumni-Peabody College (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Alumni-Roane State Community College (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Alumni-Shelby State Community College (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Alumni-Southwestern at Memphis (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Alumni-Steed College (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Alumni-Tennessee State University (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Alumni-Tennessee Tech (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Alumni-Tennessee Wesleyan College (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Alumni-UT Chattanooga (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Alumni-UT Knoxville (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Alumni-UT Martin (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Alumni-UT Nashville (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Alumni-Vanderbilt (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Alumni-Volunteer State Community College (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Alumni-Walters State Community College (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - 13th G.A. Financial (Box 15)
    - Lillard Administration Mailing Statements (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Lillard Administration Bank Receipts (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Money Receipts Book (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Money Receipts Book (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - TISL Checks (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Balance Book (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 13th G.A. Financial (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 14th General Assembly (Box 16)
    - Convention Details 14th G.A. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Blue Book Drafts (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - TISL Delegate Manual (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - TISL Delegate Manual Drafts (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Registration Figures (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Directory of Officers 14th G.A. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - General Memoranda (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Executive Council (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Mike Brink, Lt. Governor (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Staff Members 14th G.A. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Kathy Scoggins, Secretary of State (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Terry Rodgers, Speaker Pro Tempore Senate (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Doug Littlejohn, Speaker of the House (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Bert Bowes, Speaker Pro Tempore House (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Matt Lipscomb, Treasurer TISL Foundation (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - David Lillard, Senior Counselor (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Tennessee Government Officials (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Awards (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 14th General Assembly (Box 17)
    - Elections (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Speeches (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Committees (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Small School Caucus (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Postal Permit (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Capitol Park Inn (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Recruiting (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Post TISL (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Letters of Congratulations (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Tony Seaton, State Board of Regents (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Presidents Council (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - WATS Line (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Survey (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - SGA Info Sheets (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Addresses (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Mailing List (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - TISL Legislation Background (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Moot Bills (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Bills Passed through Senate (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Legislation (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Legislation (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 14th General Assembly (Box 18)
    - Receipts and Invoices (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Info Sheets A-M (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Info Sheets N-Z (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Travel (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer’s Reports (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Brenda Sanders: State Treasurer (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Expense Authorization Form (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Expense Reports (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Mailing (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Finances, General (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Bank Statements (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Receipts & Invoices (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Monthly Income (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Apportionment (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - 15th General Assembly (Box 19)
    - 15th G.A. General (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Frank Anderson (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 15th G.A. Blue Book (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 14th G.A. Delegate Directory (Published for 15th G.A.) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 15th G.A. Tax Documents (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Pre-Filed Legislation Procedure (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Committee Agenda Ditto Forms (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Legislation Amendment Forms (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bills to Committee (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Herron-Dodd Resolution (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Photographs (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - 15th G.A. Priority Bills (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Bills not making Priority List (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - TISL Bill Originals (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Bottle Resolution (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Page’s Resolution (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Littlejohn Resolution (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - TISL Bills 001-019 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - 15th General Assembly Bills (Box 20)
    - TISL Bills 021-052, 054, 068 (excluding 049) (Box 20)
  - 16th General Assembly (Box 21)
    - 16th G.A. General (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 16th G.A. Governance (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - TISL Delegate Manual (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - TISL Blue Book (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Executive Council (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - TISL Foundation (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 16th G.A. Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Application for Committee Officers (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Committee Officer Application Forms (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Delegate Info Sheets (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Expenditure Reports (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Directories (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Priority Bills (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 16th G.A. Legislation (Box 22)
    - Bills 001-068 (Excluding: 019, 026, 049, 060, 063) (Box 22)
  - 17th General Assembly (Box 23)
    - Correspondence 17th G.A. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Executive Council 17th G.A. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Delegate Packet 17th G.A. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Delegate Info Sheets (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Delegate Manual (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - TISL Endowment (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Forms (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Legislation 001-045 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Legislation 046-080 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 18th General Assembly (Box 24)
    - 18th G.A. General (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - TISL Foundation 18th G.A. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Alumni List (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - TISL Endowment (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - TISL Executive Council (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Black Caucus (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 18th G.A. Priority Legislation (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 18th G.A. Bills-Incomplete (Box 24)
  - 19th General Assembly (Box 25)
    - 19th G.A. Bluebook (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Bills 001-0068 (Box 25)
  - 20th General Assembly (Box 26)
    - Welcome from Governor Ross (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Tentative Agenda (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - 20th G.A. General (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - TISL Delegate Manual (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Officer List (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - TISL Foundation (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 20th GA Blue Book (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - TISL Expansion Plan 1/2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - TISL Expansion Plan 2/2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Executive Council (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - IRS/ TN Tax (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Financial (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Annual Fund (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - HJR 240 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Hotel Reservations (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Committee Officer Applications (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Fact Sheet (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - TISL Member List (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Priority Legislation (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - 20th G.A. (Box 27)
    - Bills 001-070 (Box 27)
  - 21st-23rd General Assemblies (Box 28)
    - 21st G.A. Address, Jeff Wilson (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Sasser’s Address to the Senate- Congressional Record (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 21st G.A. General (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 22nd G.A. General (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 1986 Alumni List 1 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 1986 Alumni List 2 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 23rd G.A. General (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 23rd G.A. Delegate Manual (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Financial 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Fund-Raising 1990’s (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - TISL Appropriations Bill (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - 30th-31st General Assemblies (Box 29)
    - 30th G.A. Delegate Manual (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, Education (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, Business, Taxation, Finance (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, General Welfare (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, Higher Education (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, Internal Affairs (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, Judiciary (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, State & Local Government (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 30th G.A. Bills, Transportation & Energy (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 31st G.A. Bluebook (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 31st G.A. UTK 30th Anniversary (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - 31st G.A. Delegate Manual (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, General Welfare (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Judiciary (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Higher Education (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Education (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, State & Local Government (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Transportation & Energy (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Business, Taxation, Finance (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Internal Affairs (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - 31st G.A. Bills, Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - 32nd-33rd General Assemblies (Box 30)
    - TISL Constitution Reprints (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 32nd G.A. Pre-TISL Handbook (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 32nd G.A. Governor’s Staff (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 32nd G.A. Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 32nd G.A. Financial (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 32nd G.A. Delegate Manual (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, Judiciary (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, Higher Education (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, Transportation & Energy (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, Education (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, Environment (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, State & Local Government (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, Business, Taxation, Finance (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - 32nd G.A. Bills, General Welfare (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - 33rd G.A. General Info. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - 33rd G.A. Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - TISL Information Session 1999 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - 33rd G.A. Bluebook (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - 33rd G.A. Delegate Manual (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, Business, Taxation, Finance (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - 33rd G.A. Bills, Education (Box 30, Folder 21)